qualidator.com 2010-11-16

# Qualidator - website quality validation & monitoring - About Us - Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement**  
seven49.net is pleased to welcome you on our website and to register your interest in our company and in our products. We take the security of your data seriously and want to make sure that you feel comfortable when visiting our internet site. Protecting your private sphere when processing your personal data is very important to us and we take this into account in our business practices.  
Personal data gathered during the visit of our websites are treated in accordance with the current laws in Switzerland. Websites of seven49.net may contain links to third-party websites, which are not cover by this data protection statement. Please take some time to read the following document, which will inform you how we treat your personal data.

**Purpose of data gathering**   
seven49.net implements personal data of website users for the technical management of the websites, for the administration of customer lists, for product surveys and for marketing purposes, i.e. to keep customers updated about the latest product announcements, special offers and any other development which we belief are of interest to our customers. This is carried out only to the extent necessary for the afore-mentioned purposes.

**Data gathering**  
The gathering of personal data (which allows unique identification of website users), is completely optional and processed through contact forms available on the website. Anonymous data is received by seven49.net through online connection and electronic traffic between the users‘ computer, the network and our servers. These data often contain information about the network routing (where the users are coming from), the equipment (what browser is being used), date and time of the visit. These data do not allow a definite identification of the website visitors and are gathered for purely statistical reasons. So-called cookies are used by seven49.net for technical purposes only, no personal data are captured through cookies.

**Transmission of personal data**  
seven49.net does basically not pass personal data on to third parties. However, seven49.net does co-operate with partners who could offer additional services to seven49.net customers.   
Data is only passed on to trustworthy partners after consent is received by customers. The treatment of personal data by seven49.net partners is not covered by this Privacy Statement. Please contact the relevant partners directly.

**Opt-in / Opt-out**   
seven49.net always leaves users the choice to receive marketing e-mails. Should you no longer wish to receive marketing e-mails from seven49.net, please let us know by mail to info@seven49.net .

**Right to information / Access to personal data  
**You can access your data stored on our servers at any time. You can view and amend your personal contact details at any time. Should you wish to view personal data which seven49.net may have saved, please send an e-mail to info@seven49.net .

**Security**  
seven49.net applies physical, electronical and administrative procedures to protect the data supplied.

**Contact us  
**Should you have any query, suggestion or complaint regarding the processing of your personal data, please contact us directly by telephone on +41 41 500 10 60 (during business hours) or by e-mail at info@seven49.net .

**Note  
**The strategy applied by seven49.net to protect individual rights can be changed at any time. Please review this page regularly for potential changes.
